 const qna = [
     {
         question: "When did Nigeria gain her independence?",
         options: ["1990", "1945", "1960", "1970"],
         answer: "1960"
     },
     {
         question: "What is Nigeria's population (in millions)?",
         options: ["180", "200", "140", '160'],
         answer: '180'
     },
     {
         question: "Which isn't a state in Nigeria?",
         options: ['Delta', 'Kano', "Benin", 'Kaduna'],
         answer: "Benin"
     },
     {
         question: "What is the national currency?",
         options: ['Pounds', 'Cefa', 'Euro', 'Naira'],
         answer: "Naira"
     },
     {
        question: "What country colonized Nigeria?",
        options: ['Russia', 'Britain', 'USA', 'Israel'],
        answer: 'Britain'
     },
     {
         question: "Which is the first capital city?",
         options: ['Ibadan', 'Lagos', 'Delta', 'Kano'],
         answer: 'Lagos'
     },
     {
        question: "Which is the current capital city in Nigeria?",
        options: ['Abuja', 'Kaduna', 'Osun', 'Lagos'],
        answer: 'Abuja'
     },
     {
         question: "Which was the first church in Nigeria?",
         options: ['St. Luke', 'St. Peters', 'St. Michael', 'St. John'],
         answer: "St. Peters"
     },
     {
         question: 'What year was Muhammadu Buhari re-elected as Nigeria\'s president?',
         options: ['1998', '2018', '2015', '2019'],
         answer: '2019'
     },
     {
         question: 'How many main languages are there in Nigeria?',
         options: ['3', '5', '7', '2'],
         answer: '3'
     }
 ]